Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
So, you're here for a good thing.
Malhun Hatun.
We...
came here as Umur Bey invited us.
However, he's not here.
We don't know what's going on, Malhun
Hatun.
It looks like you didn't
know that we were coming.
You don't know where Umur Bey is.
It seems he has some work to do.
Or else, he would be here.
Yes, my Sheikh.
He will come.
Then we'll see what is happening.
Whatever.
We can't be here any longer.
My Sheikh.
We should go.
He may come any moment.
I am sure he will come.
Osman Bey is right.
We can't wait any longer.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful)
Send our
regards to Umur Bey, Malhun Hatun.
Tell him we
want to hear what he will say about it.
- My Sheikh.
My Bey.
Nikola still isn't here.
My Bey. I am afraid that
Nikola may do something bad.
Why would he do that, Bahadır?
He hates Togay as much as I do.
Why would he endanger his own prosperity?
He will come.
He will definitely come.
The price of the betrayal is paid with
a sacrifice.
Where are you, father?
Where are you?
My Bey, he's still not here.
What will we do?
We can't go back, Bahadır.
Look at the way where
Nikola will come from.
We will deal with him if he's not there.
We can sacrifice our lives if we should.
Your command, my Bey.
Come on.
My Allah, help us.
It's a trap!
Be careful!
Stay together Alps!
Togay!
The hunter becomes the hunted, Umur Bey.
Alps!
Attack!
Mongols are coming!
For blood, for the love of blood...
to Erlik Khan.
Their dead bodies are for Erlik Khan!
Don't have mercy on them!
Kill them all!
I finally found you, Umur Bey.
I'll cut your bloody hands, Togay!
I'll give your soul to Erlik Khan.
Togay!
Archers!
My Allah, what have I done?
Kill them!
Kill them all!
You came back quickly, my Osman.
How are Umur Bey and Malhun Hatun?
Umur Bey wasn't there.
We didn't talk about anything.
Should I set a table for you?
I am not hungry, my Bala.
Okay, then.
I'll go back to working.
That's enough!
Let's go!
Mother.
Help me.
Let me look at you.
Come here.
Don't be afraid.
Alaca.
Put out the fire.
Start the treatments of the wounded.
First, children.
Children are primary.
Father.
Where are you, father?
Where are you?
Umur Bey's story has ended.
We are leaving!
Why did he do that?
Why did he invite us if he was reluctant?
Why did he leave if he was eager?
There's something wrong, Bamsı Bey.
It will be out soon.
- Do you think something bad happened?
- I hope not.
However, I can't think of anything
other than that.
- Can I come in?
- Come in.
My Bey, we have news from Umur Bey.
Tell me.
My Bey.
Camu.
He attacked our tent.
What are you saying?
My Bey, they attacked Umur Bey too.
Togay attacked our Bey too.
How is Umur Bey? How is Malhun Hatun?
Tell me.
They are alive and well.
Thank Allah.
We have lost so many people, Osman Bey.
They broke us.
- They ruined us.
- Ssssh.
Don't lower your head.
We will take their revenge.
We will take revenge of the Alps
that fought with Umur Bey...
and innocent people who are attacked.
May Allah bless you, Osman Bey.
Didn't we deal with Togay?
Liars don't keep their
promises, Osman Bey.
- Göktuğ.
- My Bey.
Boran.
Get ready.
- We are going to Umur Bey's tent.
- Your command, my Bey.
Bamsı Bey.
We won't be trapped.
You say here.
Take some precautions.
It seems that Togay won't
stick to the agreement.
Don't worry, Osman Bey.
I will kill them if they come here.
Brother.
Come on.
Come on, brother.
What have I done, Bahadır?
What have I done?
I was fooled.
I became a victim of the desire of revenge
that possessed my soul.
My Alps...
women, innocent children...
I am the only guilty one.
Only me.
Father.
You are wounded.
I was fooled by Nikola.
It was a trick of him saying we would
kill Togay together.
Togay knew that.
He raided my unprotected tent.
Open your eyes, Gökçe.
Gökçe!
My Bey! What did they do to us?
She is dying!
Father.
Let me look at your wound.
My wound is in...
my heart.
There's no cure for it.
Victory!
Victory! Victory!
Umur Bey.
He won't be able to recover.
Osman is next.
Geyhatu's judge...
what about his order?
He will understand he can't make himself
listened to the Turks...
by giving orders from the palace.
I am the owner of this region.
Umur Bey learned his lesson.
He won't tie us down anymore.
Umur Bey...
does he do this without telling Osman?
Osman...
I have just one agreement with you.
And that is...
death.
Victory!
Osman Bey is here.
I am sorry, sisters and brothers.
Brother.
- You will be fine.
- Thank you, Osman Bey.
- She will be okay, Inshallah.
- Inshallah.
Umur Bey.
Malhun Hatun.
Your pain is our pain, your
sorrow is our sorrow.
I am sorry for your losses.
The martyrs' graves show that...
these lands are yours forever.
However, we will take their revenge.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Tell me.
How did they do it?
They raided our tent after you
left with Sheikh Edebali.
Umur Bey.
You weren't in the tent
when we came here.
Togay took advantage of it.
A dispute happened
between the herdsmen and Byzantine
because of the grass.
I went there to understand what happened.
Our agreement with Togay doesn't
make any sense anymore.
You be careful.
I left my Alps here for the tent's safety.
Don't worry.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Umur Bey...
get some rest.
I will come here again later.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Is your father dead too?
I never had a father.
My mother and my father is...
my tent.
So is yours.
You will have a Bey. You will have
children.
The honor of your father...
you will carry it with your children.
Proudly.
When...
the tears fell to the lands...
hope will grow in those lands.
Selcan and Bala will be exiled.
Father.
- How will you treat me as your father?
- When you start to behave like my father!
I am not your daughter!
You are not my father!
I said you can kill him
even if the traitor is my father.
Whatever the traditions say
should be done.
We disturbed the balances
as we didn't go to war.
War is like a balance.
My plan is working.
We will have great news.
Our actual enemy is Togay.
We would kill him if we went to war.
My soldiers are alive.
My enemies' soldiers are...
killing each other.
We should have attacked Togay
when Umur Bey was with us.
Umur Bey...
Togay must have killed him.
Nikola, we have some news.
Togay destroyed Umur's army and his tent.
What were we saying? The actual war
starts now!
Osman's promise...
is spoiled.
Umur will hope for help from Osman.
And Osman will attack Togay.
What if Osman doesn't attack Togay?
Then...
Togay will attack Osman.
Then, what will we do?
Without losing a soldier...
we will watch them kill each other.
When their war is over...
we will be done with...
the rest of the bugs.
All of them!
Why didn't Togay stick to the agreement?
There's something behind it.
Togay isn't trustworthy.
As he doesn't need a reason
to not keep his word.
We will be ready.
He won't stop as he attacked Umur Bey.
However, there may be...
another reason for him
to not keep his word.
We should learn this.
Brother, how are the preparations going?
We are taking precautions around Sögüt
and the tents.
We are ready for a sudden attack.
Eyvallah (okay).
We still keep working to extend
precautions, Osman Bey.
Osman Bey...
sooner or later, the thing
behind all this will be apparent.
If we are sure that Togay will attack...
why don't we attack first?
Togay has more soldiers than before.
And...
He can predict our attack.
The outcome of attacking a prepared
and crowded enemy...
can be heavy.
You are right, Osman Bey, but...
That we are just watching while
he attacks Umur Bey...
may show us weak.
It may encourage the enemy.
It may let our friends down.
We will wait Togay to make a mistake.
When the conditions are satisfied...
We raise our flag and say
Takbir (Allah is the greatest).
Inshallah. (If Allah permits).
Mashallah. (Praises).
I've made a mistake.
I paid dearly for my mistake.
This was a painful warning.
My Lord tells me I'm taking the
wrong way...
My daughter tells the same.
Her eyes tell me I'm taking
the wrong way...
Tells me that I've destroyed everything.
You are taking the wrong way, father.
You've made a mistake.
You still keep doing it.
I heard while you were talking to Bahadır.
I know you left the tent to attack Togay.
This is why Togay attacked our tent,
right?
We made a plan with Nicola.
But he left me alone.
He wanted to...
bait us to Togay.
Trusting Nicola aside, doing all of these
without telling Osman Bey was also wrong.
Now it is a worse mistake that
you are hiding it from Osman Bey.
I lost so many soldiers...
The innocents...
They even slaughtered the innocents.
My Bey, Osman Bey has to know it was us
who attacked Togay.
This means his agreement with Togay
has been violated.
His tribe is under danger.
He needs to take precaution.
Today...
I was going to talk to him...
but I couldn't...
I didn't want to embrass myself
to Osman Bey...
while our pain was fresh.
I couldn't take it.
But, the first thing to do tomorrrow is...
to talk Osman Bey about this.
Malhun.
What is Gokce's situation?
She is still fighting for her life.
We placed observes on the ways.
We placed archers everywhere.
What about the bridges?
Two has been made unusable.
The ways Togay can take has been decreased
in number.
We'll try to end them before coming here.
But if they manage to come here,
we'll have the final strike here.
Kayı Tribe is ready to fight.
Now I want to see Sogut.
My Bey.
- Tell me, Baysungur.
- My Bey...
A Mongol soldier was carrying a chest.
He left the chest when our observers
chased him.
Open it.
Take it my Bey.
It is from Togay.
He said our agreement was violated...
when Umur Bey tried to attack him.
He says its my and Kayı tribe's turn.
All the ambition, all the vanity
led him a huge mistake like this.
If this is true...
Then...
this means he disobeyed me.
I'll make him pay for this.
You don't need to go to him, Osman Bey.
Here they are coming.
Let him come.
Salam Aleikum
(peace be upon you)
Aleikum Salam.
(Peace be upon you too.)
Osman Bey, we have to talk about
something important.
Come here Umur Bey.
Come here.
Umur Bey.
Is this true?
Tell me.
It is true.
What the hell are you saying?
Umur Bey...
we shall go to my tent.
I can hardly hide my anger.
Let's go.
Brother.
I'll make you pay in my tent.
Malhun Hatun.
You shall not come.
I'll see Umur Bey face to face.
I didn't know.
We are aware, Malhun Hatun.
Don't worry.
Let Beys talk it through.
We consent you.
I hope everything goes well.
Inshallah
(If Allah permits)
I give my condolences to you, Malhun Hatun
I heard what happened.
May Allah bless you, thanks Bala Hatun.
Thank Lord you are fine.
My Allah protected me.
That Togay and Osman Bey's agreement
is violated doesn't bode well.
There's something wrong in this.
Come, have a rest.
We came to your tent yesterday.
With my Sheik Edebalı
and my brother Gündüz.
We waited for you to keep your
promise and come.
But you didn't show up.
Where were you?
Didn't we warn you...
not to get in action alone?
Didn't you troubled us each time?
You still do what you want to do, huh?
You lost many alps.
You took many innocents' life.
You endangerd all the Turks!
For what?
Tell me Umur Bey.
Why?
I told you I agreed with Sultan.
We set a plan!
You destroyed it all!
I found myself confronting Ilhanlı State
without the support I expected to have!
Tell me.
What is the cost of that?
What is that bow for, Osman Bey?
Don't you remember this bow?
The bow my ancestor Oghuz Khan gave
to his son Günhan.
Don't you still understand that...
Günhan, the noble Kayıs are the
heir of this gifted state?
Tell me!
I told you to stand behind this bow,
not to face this bow!
You are right.
Osman Bey.
I didn't stand behind that bow.
I faced it.
Now...
I am drawing back.
Now that I am nothing but a hamper
to you...
What to do is clear now.
We will go back just like how we came.
We are going to leave this land.
This is the best call.
We shall leave, Bala Hatun.
You can go, Malhun Hatun.
What happened there?
What did Osman Bey say?
He mentioned Oghuz Khan's golden bow.
We are leaving Malhun.
Get ready.
Umur Bey seems perished.
There must have been a conflict
about merging the tribes.
Malhun Hatun is sad too.
I wonder what's going to happen
to marriage.
You have to ask this to Osman Bey,
my Gonca.
Can I come in Osman Bey?
Come!
What is it, Osman Bey?
What did Umur Bey say?
Does he realise his fault?
Will he give up on disobeying you?
Umur Bey...
won't be with us anymore.
Osman Bey, were you holding this
bow while talking to Umur Bey?
I mentioned my ancestor Oghuz Khan.
He understood what I meant.
Now, forget about Umur Bey.
Let's talk about Togay.
However you like, Osman Bey.
Togay's plan is clear.
He'll hold us responsible for
Umur Bey's attack.
And he is going to want to
do the same to us.
Then he'll see attacking Umur Bey is not
the same with attacking Kayı.
Of course he will!
If he comes here in our tent,
I'll rip his liver out..
I'll feed wolves with his body!
That day will arrive, Osman Bey.
We'll see that dog die.
Eyvallah.
No one can stop your dream.
I swear.
- We swear.
Let everyone hear that.
There are three parts of Kayı security.
We can surpass them.
- What about Sogut?
- They placed troops inside and outside.
Every troop includes twenty Alps,
excluding watchmen.
Osman Bey doubled the number of
soldiers today.
And there are wandering Alps who
check around. We have to watch out for them.
So, Osman is trying to hide his fear
by taking precautions.
He'll see precautions he took won't
save him from dying.
- Talk.
- Osman recieved your gift.
Osman is frightened.
He is going to be mad.
While he is busy with managing his
feelings, I'll strike him big time.
What is your order, Togay?
Divide the soldiers into two.
We are going to attack both their tents
and Sogut simultaneously.
We are going to infiltrate around their
tent before sunshine.
While twilight turns into red,
when they recite adhan...
and start praying to their God...
we'll let them reach to their God.
Now leave and be ready
to slaughter anyone.
In the name of dark forests...
Dark souls...
And dark...
swears...
The breath of death shall be with us.
My dark swear
shall get wet...
by Osman's blood!
We took precautions.
If Togay comes here, he won't
be able to get out of here alive.
I can't wait to fight. I would pray them
to come if it was just us.
I'll join you later.
- What is it?
- He is investigating how people are doing
Oh...
Sorry...
I didn't mean to scare you.
I am not scared.
I am just surprised.
You came out of nowhere.
Why are you looking like that?
Your eyes...
What's it?
Looks worried.
Mongols are going to attack, that's why.
Don't you see I'm here?
Why are you scared?
What does it mean that you are here?
You are in safe if I'm here.
Only me?
We have other Alps, are.
Everybody is in safe.
Aygül wait.
This is for protecting me.
Do you see Goktug over there?
I do, so what?
He is in love.
What makes you say that?
Isn't it apparent?
Observing people is a shame.
We should mind our own business.
I want to watch them.
Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
That's it.
I am a girl without father and mother.
I am a Greek living in Sogut alone.
I make my living by selling fruits.
Eat. They are fresh.
Of course they are.
Why don't you taste?
Are you shy?
He is shy.
My brother is a bit shy.
Cerkutay, what are you doing here?
Aygül insisted to see you.
Aygül!
- I can eat if you don't.
- Cerkutay.
- Give me.
- Cerkutay!
Aygül, eat it. It's delicious.
- Leave.
- We shall leave.
Cerkutay.
Walk!
They are both crazy.
I must go.
My mission is waiting.
I'll see you around.
I shall leave.
Check it if you can rip it.
- The stitches are very hard, my Sheik.
- We can't, my Sheik.
If it rips out someday, it'll start
from here.
Where it was stitched.
Salam Aleikum my Sheik.
Alaikum Salam, Osman Bey.
Alaikum Salam.
Excuse us, my Sheik.
Sit, Osman Bey.
My Sheik, you probably know the topic.
I do, Osman Bey, I do.
While I was waiting to set a peace
in my tent...
He attacked Togay to ruin
our agreement.
My Sheik, he ruined everything!
It'll cost so many people's life!
Stitching leather is difficult, Osman Bey.
Stitching two different leathers
is difficult.
Cutting it is easy.
Disconnecting them is easy.
You wanted to do the difficult.
Umur Bey chose the easy.
However, there is one other possibility.
Starting over...
Stitching it one more time with patience.
You may say "why would I bear again?"
Only the one whose aim is great
can bear it again.
Only that man can reunite everything
again.
Osman Bey is right.
We ruined everything.
We paid dearly.
We can't stay here anymore.
We'll migrate.
We'll seek Kızılbeyogulları's future
in other lands.
Where are we going to migrate, father?
This is the end.
We are on the edge.
Greeks on one side,
Mongols on the other. Where is to migrate?
Wherever possible.
I can't stay here.
You have to. We have to help Osman Bey
to carry his responbilities.
We are the ones who ruined everything.
Now we can't help him.
We are weakened.
And our reputation is shaken.
Our immigration is
the best for Osman Bey.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come in.
What's wrong, Alaca?
Had something happened?
My bey.
Gökçe has passed.
Leave me alone.
The price of this mistake...
can't be paid by the others,
Umur Bey.
They ruined your plan again, right?
Isn't it possible for the two tribes
to unite now?
How can I be together with the people
who act behind me.
He'll take his tribe and leave.
Let him do so.
What about Malhun Hatun.
She will go with him, of course.
May the outcome be good, Osman Bey.
You did everything you could
for this union.
But I failed.
My intentions are honest.
Accept me, my Allah.
The one who gives the trouble also
gives the cure.
Here, heart wounds are
getting treated...
and pain gets eased.
-Is there a cure for regret?
-There is no cure for those who don't regret.
Come with your regret.
The Mongol heathens don't show mercy to
even the women or children.
When will they leave, my sheik?
There is goodness in every evil.
Maybe the beys who caused...
those innocent people to die...
will understand their responsibilities
better and come together.
Maybe they will understand that...
the future of the Muslims depend
on this union.
Then, the Mongol heathens will leave
as they come.
My sheik, Umur Bey wants to come in.
Let him come, Akça Dervish.
I should leave, my sheik.
Come, Umur Bey.
My sheik.
I've made a mistake.
Because of my mistake...
children...
Even children died.
At this height...
Gökçe...
She was so pretty and nimble...
They killed her even.
Because of me...
Because of my ambitions...
I'm the cause of everything.
Now it's enough.
Neither Osman Bey...
nor the Turkmen Beys...
can't get no good from me.
-I should just leave--
-How easy it is...
to just leave, to give up...
to say that you failed.
What about...
the hard thing to do?
Admitting that you made a mistake.
Feeling regret.
Taking lessons.
When you are at this stage...
when you saw the results
of your ambitions...
got a great lesson,
you can't leave.
What should I do, my sheik?
I can't look at anyone in the face.
You won't think selfishly.
You will join Osman Bey's union.
You will do your part and find
forgiveness.
Turks have no other place to imigrate
to.
We'll stay here and not move.
Understand this well.
Our warriors positioned near Söğüt and
Kayı Tribe. We are ready to attack.
The spirits of twilight will offer
blood...
at dawn in the Kayı Tribe
and Söğüt!
When Turks perform salaat
for their god...
the earth will tremble and
the sky will rain blood.
My warriors will have the spoils of
the tribe and Söğüt!
Osman and his wife are mine.
The gold and the virgins are yours.
For my black oath!
Erlik Khan! Erlik Khan!
Where are you father?
''Gökçe has passed away.''
Leave me alone.
Where did you go?
Where is Umur Bey, I wonder.
He went after the ones who
seek the help of a candle...
when there is the great sun
to benefit.
He seeks the cure of regret
in a greater regret.
Malhun Hatun, where are you going?
I'm going to Osman Bey. I'm afraid
my father might act on his own.
-What is this governor doing here?
-If not to drink blood...
may the dark souls curse him.
The stripes on your face
have the color of blood.
Geyhatu's hunting dog, Togay the Dark
Shaman, where are you going?
It's time for the black oath.
Osman broke the agreement.
He sent Umur Bey after me.
I'm blessed with my black oath.
I'm ready to soak Bythinia in blood.
My warriors seek blood like
hungry wolves.
The honor belongs
to Geyhatu.
Draw your warriors back, Togay.
This attack won't happen.
Geyhatu's honor is enough to
fill the seas of the world.
What we need is gold.
Osman did not only break our agreement
but also stained my honor.
I know everything.
You gave a lesson to Umur Bey and his
tribe. He was punished.
More of it will cause a rebellion.
It's not the time for a rebellion.
We assigned you to assure stability
in these lands. Don't harm it.
Where did you learn all this?
My eyes and ears are sharper
than your weapon, Togay.
The punishment I gave Umur Bey is
giving Osman Bey strength. I can't allow it.
You are a border bey! And I'm Geyhatu's
governor.
You will obey my word, Togay.
My black oath awaits. But Osman won't
wait.
A day will come and Osman will
find power in your silence...
and then you will answer.
I'll think about that when the time comes.
Now, I've come from far.
Bring me food.
I've other places to go.
-Take care of the tribe, Gonca.
-Don't worry. Everything is fine.
-I'm going to our sheik.
-Send him my regards.
-Malhun Hatun is coming.
-What's wrong?
-Welcome, Malhun Hatun.
-Thank you, Bala Hatun.
-What's wrong, you look worried?
-I'm here to talk to Osman Bey.
Osman Bey isn't at the tribe.
Where is he? Do you know?
I need to see Osman Bey.
I don't know where he went. If something
is wrong, tell me. Maybe I can help.
Thank you, Bala Hatun. But no other
than Osman Bey can help.
-Malhun Hatun, what happened?
-He isn't here. Bala Hatun doesn't know where.
-What will we do now?
-We'll return. We might hear something there.
We can't leave the tribe empty
in such times.
We don't know what Togay will do.
Come on.
I know your anger for him, Togay!
Geyhatu trusts you. Don't lose
in your anger.
I'm not mad at him, Camuha. How did he
hear what happened so soon?
There is a spy among us.
I will find him and skin his head.
Umur Bey is coming, Togay.
How did you dare to face me, Umur Bey?
You've been chasing me for a long time.
I wanted to settle our scores.
I came to kill you with my own weapon.
Know that Osman Bey isn't involved
in what happened.
I came here to settle scores.
You came to offer your corpse to me.
Your bravery comes from your stupidity.
Give Umur Bey his sword.
If he can kill me, let him go.
What good is a jar that wasn't wet
with tears for?
Thank Allah.
I get to see my dear more frequently.
Would a physician say that to
his patient, my sheik?
My dear is sick again.
She is here again. Thank Allah.
Would he say that?
He wouldn't, Bala.
''Thank Allah, the sick came for a cure''
he would say.
Is there a cure for my sickness, my sheik?
What did Osman tell you, Bala?
Did he say that it won't happen if you
don't want?
-He did.
-But you accepted it.
After all, you care about Osman
and the tribe...
and all the Muslim world, more than
you care about yourself.
Would your god deny such altruism?
Do you know the devotion of our
mother Sare?
I know, my sheik.
To have Hz.İbrahim's lineage
live...
she consented him to marry
another woman.
Then, what happened?
Allah blessed them with...
a good child.
Our mother Sare was infertile.
And she was old.
My daughter, you prayed a lot.
You were patient.
Now, stay patient during this test.
Allah sees you and hears you.
My sheik, will Allah bless me
with a child?
Will I be a mother?
Will I hug my children?
Surely, Allah hears our prayers.
You wanted to kill me with your
sword, huh?
Then, I will kill you with your own
sword.
Your daughter Malhun won't be able
to go to your grave.
Ravens will eat your corpse!
Protect Togay!
We didn't come here to spill blood
but to remind you our agreement.
Move!
Umur Bey not only disrespected me...
but you too. He will pay.
He paid enough.
Umur Bey and his tribe is under
my protection.
In our laws, it's on me to punish
him.
It's not that easy, Osman Bey.
Not that easy.
Know it well that...
I won't leave a bey under my protection
to you to punish!
If something happens to Umur Bey...
then, our agreement is over.
We made an agreement. I will become
a vassal...
and you will get the gold.
As Genghis Khan said...
Either honor the agreement or the
law of the land...
to death.
Genghis Khan's laws on one side...
and Togay's anger on the other
side.
Which one will Geyhatu pick?
Tell me.
Your tongue is as sharp as your sword.
But not as my sword.
When the time comes...
I will unsheathe it for you.
Know that well, Osman Bey.
Now we'll freely leave here.
I want to believe that you have the
honor to not stab us on our backs.
Umur Bey.
Osman.
Back then, when I went to invade
China...
there was a bey with a tongue as
sharp as yours at Wuhan.
I locked him in a well until he died.
Do you know why?
The salvation for rebel souls
like you...
is death.
My god is a witness...
we are able to get out of the
wells we are locked in.
-You did the right thing, Togay.
-Osman thinks that he has won.
I will give him such a death that...
it will be more merciless than
a dark well.
Osman Bey.
Come, Umur Bey.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
What I did there--
What you did there was an
honorable act.
You wanted to pay with your life
for your mistake.
But I can never allow a Turkmen bey
to walk to death.
You are a man of your word, Osman Bey.
You neither give up your sword
nor your brothers.
You don't let your flag go down,
not let Muslims to get hurt.
Not at all.
Now, I'm not against you.
If you allow me, I want to stand
with you.
Osman Bey, how did you know that
I would go to Togay?
-What's wrong, Kumral Abdal?
-You decide, Osman Bey.
-Tell me then.
-I saw Umur Bey in my dream.
He was like a wounded bird. He flew away
at the dawn without speaking to anyone.
-To where?
-Wait, Osman Bey.
I went after the bird. He entered the
forest. Then, he dissappeared.
-For what?
-Like he was going to pay a price.
-He must've gone to Togay.
-Togay...
Togay will kill him.
Kumral Abdal is our light.
Thank Allah. Thank Allah, he was right.
-Osman Bey.
-Brother.
I need to take some of the alps and
go to the tribe.
Go at once, brother.
I can't trust anyone.
I will accompany Umur Bey.
Alright.
-Thank you, valiants, for not leaving us.
-Thank you, Umur Bey.
-Thank you.
-Disputes are temporal, Umur Bey.
Our brotherhood is permanent.
-Osman Bey.
-Brother.
Come on, alps. We are going to the
tribe.
Umur Bey.
Gather all the alps. We'll search every
place if we have to.
Anyone hears anything about
my father?
Unfortunately, my lady. Alps searched
everywhere but there is no sign.
Where are you, father?
Where are you?
Where were you, father?
I was worried.
Osman Bey will be our guest.
We'll talk there.
Please, sit.
I went to talk to Togay to
solve our issue.
Why did you do that, father?
How can you trust him?
-Couldn't you think that he might kill you?
-I have, my daughter.
I have. But...
I went there to pay for the mistake
I've made.
Did you go there to die?
I didn't want more innocent people...
to get hurt because of me.
And how did you get out?
When Togay was about to kill me...
Osman Bey came and saved me.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Our debt is increasing. I don't know
how we can pay.
We did our duty. There is no need
to talk about that now.
Togay issue is closed for a while.
Now, it's time to talk about
our future.
Will we still migrate in this
condition, my bey?
There is no need to talk about
that either.
Now, we are together.
No one will go anywhere.
Osman Bey is right, my daughter.
There is no separation now.
I see now who has the future
of the Turks.
Now, the matter of marriage...
that we talked with our sheik.
Malhun Hatun is not only my daughter
but also my right hand.
She carries the weight of the tribe.
She fights when needed.
Her marriage and seperation
from our tribe...
will take our strenght away.
Of course, she will marry and
leave one day.
But...
I'm not sure...
if that's the day, if I'm ready.
I believe, I will never be ready.
Osman Bey.
You shouldn't wait for me to be ready.
If you still want my daughter...
your marriage with Malhun Hatun...
is an honor for me.
Now, tell me, Malhun Hatun.
Do you have your consent for
this marriage.
You say that it's an honor for you to have
your daughter marry him, father.
An honor indeed.
But...
Osman Bey is already married.
There is a woman who waits
for her at his tribe.
You are talking about the merge
of two tribes.
But you don't mention the two
wives coming together.
It seems that Bala Hatun hardened
her heart and accepted it.
And about me...
for the well-being of two
great Turkmen tribes...
going to a tribe that already
has a Khatun...
is something I can accept.
But tell me, Osman Bey.
How will you assure justice?
My first wife and the mother
of my heir...
will stay in different tents.
Their incomes will be separated.
They'll choose their own servants.
But...
no one, and no one...
will order each other.
How will Bala Hatun see me?
You can't expect a woman to...
love another woman that
comes after her.
But she'll show respect.
And she'll expect respect.
Is the only reason you want me...
the interests of these two tribes?
Isn't there any other reason?
Of course.
Of course, there is one more reason.
Kayı Beys expect an heir from me.
And they asked me to marry again.
But I waited to meet the mother of
my heir.
-I waited to find her.
-Have you found her, Osman Bey?
I have.
Indeed I have.
With Allah's approval and the prophet's
words...
will you be my Khatun?
I will.